Take Back Your Life
Unknown is a action, mystery, thriller film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra.
A man awakens from a coma, only to discover that someone has taken on his
identity and that no one, (not even his wife), believes him.
With the help of a young woman, he sets out to prove who he is.
Dr. Martin Harris, played by Liam Neeson.
Gina, played by Diane Kruger.
Elizabeth Harris, played by January Jones.
Martin B., played by Aidan Quinn.
Ernst Jürgen, played by Bruno Ganz.
Rodney Cole, played by Frank Langella.
Unknown is a 2011 action thriller film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra and starring Liam
Neeson, Diane Kruger, January Jones, Aidan Quinn, Bruno Ganz, and Frank Langella.
The film, produced by Joel Silver, Leonard Goldberg and Andrew Rona, is based on the 2003 French novel by Didier Van Cauwelaert
published in English as Out of My Head which was adapted as the film's screenplay by Oliver Butcher and Stephen Cornwell.
The narrative centers around a professor who wakes up from a four-day long coma and sets out to prove his
identity after no one recognizes him, including his own wife, and another man claims to be him.
Released on 18 February 2011, the film received mixed reviews from critics
and grossed $136 million against its $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of hotel, taxi, coma, taxi driver, prince.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.